demonuts.com 2019-06-25

# Privacy Policy - DemoNuts

This policy was last updated on December 11,2016

DemoNuts keeps full action to respect your online privacy. The following words describes how and which type of information we collect about visitors of DemoNuts.

### **Types of information we collect**

DemoNuts collect personal identifiable information such as name, email address, and web site. Besides these three information, DemoNuts do not collect information like  contact number, banking details etc from any visitor. DemoNuts is also not getting such kind of information from any other web sites , blogs or agencies.

### **Non-personal identifiable information**

Non-personal identifiable information includes data that may correspond to a particular person, but is not sufficient to identify, contact or locate the person. DemoNuts may collect information such as type of browser, computer system specification, Device IDs,IP addresses,ISP informations,Cookies and other such informations.

### **Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file stored on a computer for various tracking purposes by websites and advertisers.Cookies are created by your Web browser. We use Cookies to enhance user experience on our Website. We never place personally identifiable information in Cookies. Additionally, our business partners (for example, advertisers) may use cookies as well. DemoNuts has no access or control of advertiser’s web cookies and is not responsible for any information stored in these types of cookies. Visitors can disable the use of cookies by changing settings of their respective web browser. However, if you disable Cookies, there might be chances that you can not access contents on our Website effectively or at all.

### **Securing and sharing your information**

We do not save,sell or rent your information with any other third parties.

### **Advertising and other links**

Visitor may find different links in DemoNuts which may be an advertisement links or can be links which are useful to visitor(for example,facebook or google developer console).Websites which are opening from  
these links may have different privacy policies and is not under the control of DemoNuts, user should click on this links at their own risk. These websites can store personal identifiable information which is bound by their own privacy policies and DemoNuts is not responsible for collecting these information nor we have access to these informations. Different advertisers like google can use cookies to serve ads in better way based on the visit and surfing of the user via different web sites. DemoNuts have not any control on these cookies and thus, is not  
responsible for information collected by these cookies.

### **Contents and Source code**

All the contents and source code downloaded from this site is the property of DemoNuts and can be used for personal education purpose only. Visitors are not allowed to use,copy or re-post the source code to any business  
or commercial blogs.

### **Terms of use**

To use DemoNuts, you must accept this privacy policy. If you are using this web site,then it is considered that you are accepting above privacy policy and not have any objections against it.

### **Modification of privacy policy**

Privacy policy of DemoNuts is subject to change without any prior notice to visitors. DemoNuts can modify this privacy policy as and when required.We hold rights to add, update and replace any conditions covered in this privacy policy. We will always display the date when last modification is made to this privacy policy at the top of this page.  
If you have any questions feel free to contact us.
